kippt.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy - Kippt

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Kippt we have a few fundamental principles:

  * **We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.**
  * **We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.**
  * **We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.**

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support team.

Kippt Inc. (“Kippt”) operates website kippt.com. It is Kippt’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

* * *

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Kippt collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Kippt’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Kippt’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Kippt may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Kippt also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Kippt’s websites choose to interact with Kippt in ways that require Kippt to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Kippt gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Kippt are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Kippt collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Kippt. Kippt does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

This Application does not support “do not track” requests.

### Aggregated Statistics

Kippt may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Kippt may monitor the most popular links or screen the links help identify spam. Kippt may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Kippt does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Kippt discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Kippt’s behalf or to provide services available at Kippt’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Kippt’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Kippt will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Kippt discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Kippt believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Kippt, third parties or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of an Kippt website and have supplied your email address, Kippt may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Kippt and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Kippt takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Kippt uses cookies to help Kippt identify and track visitors, their usage of Kippt website, and their website access preferences. Kippt visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Kippt’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Kippt’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If Kippt, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Kippt goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Kippt may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Kippt may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Kippt’s sole discretion. Kippt encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

* * *

CC BY-SA 2.5. Modified from [Automattic](http://www.automattic.com/) Privacy Policy
